# Adam C. Burrill

adamcburrill@gmail.com

971 599-1228

Passionate about helping organizations and their employees make optimal use of technology.

## Personal Strengths

I have more than 12 years experience in technical support roles. I am a systems thinker who enjoys solving problems by looking at technical and individual needs. I am very patient in a crisis and use my excellent listening abilities to find solutions that are collaborative and inclusive.

#### **Skill Sets**

- Customer service, stakeholder focused and inclusive so that solutions are optimal
- Workstation support on Windows 7, 8 and 10, MacOS, Linux and Chromebook; including OS imaging and distribution
- Mobile support of Android, iOS
- Software support, desktop and server, including Microsoft Office
- Hardware installation, repair, troubleshooting
- Virtualization from multiple vendors, including servers and remote access workstations
- TCP/IP, DNS, routers, cabling, internet, LANs, WANs, VPNs, hardware, connectivity
- Windows Server support, Active Directory, Exchange, cloud solutions

#### Experience

## System Administrator Burrill Technology Consulting 2007 to Now

Part-time business supporting individuals and small businesses with technology needs. Advised on purchasing, upgrades and security enhancements. Installed LANs, WAPs, internet access, PCs, Macs, printers, iPhones and Android phones. Provided technical support for hardware and software. Maintained websites and online discussion boards.

### Small Business Owner Spring and Autumn Healthcare 2011 to Now

Managed all aspects of health care business including contracting with outside vendors, patient care, medical billing, marketing and promotion, customer retention, website management and technology.

## Systems Administrator Olympic Eagle Distributing 2003 to 2007

Maintained IT infrastructure for a beverage distribution company with 200+ employees. Designed a network for a new warehouse that tied together multiple nodes on a WAN. Supported and upgraded legacy business software with 100+ mobile sales, warehouse and

delivery devices. Installed new fleet of rugged mobile devices. Interfaced with external vendors to provide additional technology and support as needed.

**Network Administrator Pioneer Human Services**1998 to 2003

Supported network, Macs and PCs on a wide-area network with 20 locations. Administration

for Exchange Server, Active Directory and Windows Server.

Lead Provider Outside In 2012-2020

Created, planned and implemented new billing systems, new procedures for coding and charting; increased training for interns and providers to ensure appropriate payment for services.

Network Support Technician Battelle Seattle Research Center 1996 - 1998

Supported network and workstations

Computer Lab Support Seattle Central Community College 1995 - 1996

Desktop Support Tech,

Lab Support Lead, Seattle University 1992-1995

**Education** 

Network+ Certification from Comptia Current

Seattle University, B.Sc. Physics

Extensive mathematics, detailed lab work, modeling physical systems with software

References available by request